adamoads.com 2016-11-28

# ADAMO

Please read following document before using the site or submitting any personal information to ADAMO.

By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted on this. We are encouraging you to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

#### Collection of Information

ADAMO collects Personal Information from our users for contact and verification purposes, including but not limited to: name, telephone number, addresses and identification documents.

We do not share, sell or otherwise distribute Personal Information to third-party companies.

#### Distribution of Information

We will only use your information for legitimate purposes of which you will be informed unless we are required to do otherwise for legal reasons.

#### Cookie/Tracking Technology

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies can also help customize the site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

#### Distribution of Information

We will only use your information for legitimate purposes about which you have been informed unless we are required to do otherwise for legal reasons.

#### Accuracy of your Information

We will ensure that information about you is accurate and up to date when we collect or use it. You can help us to achieve this by keeping us informed of any changes to the information we hold about you.

#### Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is important to us and that's why it's kept secure. Only authorized ADAMO employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information.

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us through our contact page.

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted on ADAMO Privacy Policy page.
